(Satori Shun) I love you.
(Hattori Maika) Me too.
The manager will be in Osaka in two weeks.
You will have to be transferred.
yes….
Maybe ➡
To separate me and Maika ➡
My mother is
It may be something that was set up.
(Yugo) This is Kato Yugo from the same team.
thank you.
(Photon) Oh, what's wrong? Suddenly.
You know why I came, right?
Maika's transfer
Did your mother do it?
(Photon) What's that about?
Please don't be fooled.
When I'm away ➡
Met her
I've heard it from Akiyama.
Listen to what happened at that time
It hits me.
At this time
It's too unnatural to have her only transferred.
For a new project
If you hear you're going to be involved ➡
Leave you alone quickly
It doesn't seem like I've gone. ➡
Being separated ➡
I wonder how long it will last
You guys.
♬〜
📱(Manner mode)
Hattori-san ➡
Thank you for your hard work.
Ah, sorry, at a strange time
I called out to him.
Ah, no.
📱(Manner mode)
Ah... it's okay.
but….
Ahhh...➡
Because it was from him
It's probably going to be long.
Ah, that's right.
sorry.
Ah, no.
Long distance relationship
Are you lonely after all?
Ah, that's right.
Sometimes I feel lonely though ➡
Right now, anyway
I'm desperate to get used to the job.
Hattori-san, do you like sweets?
Ah yes I love it.
(Yugo) In this neighborhood
There's a delicious cake shop.
The Baumkuchen there is excellent.
That's right.
I'll buy it next time.
I'm sure it's near the head office ➡
Delicious Baumkuchen restaurant
There was, right?
I also liked that place.
I know.
I often went shopping too.
Haha.
Kato-san
Maybe a sweet tooth?
⚞Konkonkon (knokku)
⚞Gacha (door sound)
(Akiyama)
President It's about time for dinner.
Ah, I'm going now.
♬〜
Tap... (Mobile operation sound)
📱(Ringtone)
📱(Audio guidance)
At the answering machine service center ➡
Connect.
(Yugo) with the Marketing Division
Get collaborative ➡
The appeal and worldview of this service
A story that is more conveyed strongly ➡
together
I want to create it.
(Male employee)
Then, with Taylor from LA.
I think the meeting should be carried out.
(Yugo) Hmm...
(Male employee) People from the Development Department
It would be better to have a few people.
(Nozomi) Ah, sorry ➡
How to use this shared space
I'd like to discuss it a little.
(Male employee)
surely. For inbound ➡
Events and so on
Maybe it can be done.
(Male employee) Ah, too
The operating rate on weekdays is declining ➡
I would like to discuss that as well.
(Nozomi) Check out...
(Voice of the heart)≪Half of the content
I couldn't understand≫
(Yugo)Thank you for your hard work. ➡
OK?
Sorry for the time being.
(Yugo) Ha ha. Hattori-san is
I've just been transferred ➡
There's nothing to worry about.
but….
If you have any problems
Please ask anything.
yes.
(Male employee) You're so tired. First.
(Male employee) Thank you for your hard work.
♬〜
📱(Manner mode)
📱(Ringtone)
♬〜
Hmm...
Hmm.
(Yugo)Thank you for your hard work.
Ah, thank you for your hard work.
yes.
Huh?
You're doing your best.
Don't overdo it too much.
Ah... thank you.
Ah
Um... I have something I want to ask.
yeah?
Here
It's a workflow though ➡
Still from each department
I can't grasp the strengths.
The operating rate on weekdays
Sometimes it's falling ➡
You can see it in this document.
For example, for business customers.
Weekdays only plans
What do you think?
Check-out until 2pm
I'll allow it to be extended ➡
The space you currently have is too much to have ➡
As a working space
Maybe make it available...
I see.
📱(Manner mode)
The loyalty program
Enhancement is effective but ➡
For attracting customers on weekdays
You need a different approach.
📱(Ringtone)
♬〜
"Good luck with your work!"
What...
I
Are you going to Tokyo and giving a presentation?
Before this
What Hattori suggested?
It was well received in the company too➡
To clients too
I want to suggest it. ➡
Because it's time for me
I want to ask Hattori-san.
Ah... but
I can still present outside. ➡
It's not packed...
(Yugo) I'm on a business trip next week ➡
Time to brush up
There is.
I agree.
(Yugo) I'll do something like this
I'm involved in a big project.
What you don't challenge
It's a waste.
Yes I'll give it a try.
♬〜
First, let's review the previous proposal.
(Nozomi) Hattori-san, first.
Thank you for your hard work.
(Nozomi) Thank you for your hard work.
(Male employee) Well, me too.
♬〜
Yeah
I think it's well organized.
Ah... that's good.
Kato's
Thanks to the advice.
The actual performance
Let's relax and do our best.
yes.
📱
Tap
hello.
📱 Maika?
Finally connected.
Sorry late at night.
Ah
No, I'm about to go home now.
Until this late?
I guess I can't get back to the head office soon?
I'll try moving.
Ah, no, it's fine.
The task I was entrusted with
Because I want to do my best.
I understand.
Maika is strong.
Everyone in the branch office was very kind too.
The environment is good so I think I can do my best.
📱 When will we meet?
I want to go there
I can't have time.
In a presentation next week
I was going to Tokyo.
Ah, that's right. Can I stay?
It's a day trip.
I see.
It's probably a while before we can meet again.
I agree.
I look forward to seeing you
I'll do my best at work.
Hey...➡
Isn't it lonely not being able to meet me?
Huh?
I'm not like Maika ➡
Become a long distance
I'm depressed though.
That's it...
I also want to meet you.
♬〜
📱 I want to meet you right now too.
Maika isn't enough.
♬〜
⚟(Yugo) Hattori-san!
Ah, thank you for your hard work.
📱 The senior who is taking care of me
Stay by your side. ➡
everytime
I'm getting support. ➡
Ah
He is also a team leader.
I'm really helping.
That's right.
📱 (Yugo) Let's go home together.
📱 Ah yes.
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Yes... will you go home together?
📱 I'm close to Kato-san.
Ahh...➡
That's right.
📱 I'll call again when I get home.
Yeah.
I understand.
Tsutenkaku is...
(Yugo) Do you know?
yes. in front
I went when I came on a trip.
(Yugo) Yes!
Did you just see it? Have you climbed?
I've climbed.
Yes, I see.
yes.
And yet, that's around
Kushikatsu and more.
Wow, I want to eat kushikatsu.
Kushikatsu. What's left...
Ah, that's right.
I bought this during lunch break
I was planning to give it to you tomorrow.
Huh?
Ah, thank you for the nutritional drink.
Always be considerate
They also helped me with overtime...
I'm grateful.
Ah...
Thanks to Kato-san ➡
Me too, a little
I think I've grown.
I'm sure I was tired
Please take a good rest.
Thank you for your hard work.
Tap...
📱(Ringtone)
hello.
Yes, things are going well.
Leave it to Hattori Maika.
⚟Kong Kong
⚟Gatcha
(Akiyama) President.
(Akiyama) Here.
So, install this system ➡
Improve overall business efficiency
There is a need to try.
This system
The cost reduction effect when introduced is:
Compared to conventional systems
It is expected to be over 30%.
Furthermore, not only is it possible to improve business efficiency
Improved information management...
Thank you for today.
(Yugo) Here it is➡
It takes time
thank you very much.
It was a really good proposal.
I'll consider it positively.
I'll contact you later.
yes. thank you.
(Yugo) Please.
Well then.
♬〜
Hehe.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ah, thank you very much.
Let's go.
yes.
Yes, it's over safely.
ah~
I think the feel was good.
I'm heading home with Kato-san now.
yes. Ah
I'll let you know when I come to work tomorrow.
Kato-san.
I've reported it.
Thank you for your hard work.
Shall we eat it for lunch too?
yes.
Chilling Chilling (bicycle bell)
(Yugo) It's dangerous!
I... sorry. OK?
Ah, it's okay. ➡
Shall we go?
yes.
♬〜
(Yugo) So, for your hard work,
I'll have a feast.
Ah, thank you very much.
Ah... um... before that ➡
Can you wait a minute?
Huh?
I'll go back soon.
Ah...
♬~(BGM in the hotel)
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
My wrist hurts a while ago.
Ah, bothering me...
Because it's my fault...
Haha, that's a big deal.
oh dear
But it certainly hurt a little.
thank you.
on second thoughts.
Please show me a moment.
Ah, no...
Please show your wrist.
(Yugo) It's fine.
It's definitely swollen.
Even if you put a compress on it
If the swelling doesn't seem to go away
Please go to the hospital.
That's fine, about that. ➡
You'll get used to the pain quickly.
♬~(BGM in the hotel)
No matter what pain
Once you get used to it, you'll get paralyzed ➡
I won't feel anything.
So don't worry.
♬~(BGM in the hotel)
Get used to the pain
Please don't say it.
♬~(BGM in the hotel)
When there's someone you can trust nearby ➡
I don't need to bear it
Because there isn't.
⚟Teen (Eleveter arrival sound)
What are your plans after this?
(Akiyama) At Daikanyama at 4pm➡
It's a meeting.
After that, it starts at 6pm...
Hattori-san.
yes.
Something's under my eyes.
What?
Please close your eyes a little.
yes. sorry.
♬〜
What are you doing?
Shun-san.
Ah
Um... I mentioned this before ➡
I'm taking care of you at my new place
This is Kato, the team leader.
Um... I'm sure you know
This is Satori Shun.
It's the person I'm dating...
(Yugo) What is Hattori's girlfriend?
Was it the president?
Ah, well...
(Yugo) President Satori Thank you for your hard work.
Greetings are good.
I'm asking what you did.
(Yugo) Umm... ah
The presentation meeting is over ➡
I think I'll do it for lunch too.
That's not the case.
Now you are
He asks Maika what she did.
(Yugo)
What... Ah, on Hattori's face➡
There was something there so
I just took it. ➡
Maybe
Did you misunderstand it? ➡
Ah... the president
What you might be worried about is
Because there's nothing
rest assured.
It's true. There's nothing.
♬~(BGM in the hotel)
I see.
It seems I was wrong.
Maika Come a little.
Ah yes.
Really nothing is done?
yes.
♬〜
Shun?
Because there's really nothing.
♬〜
Shun-san ➡
I've only seen Shun.
Yeah.
sorry. Getting long distance ➡
He seemed a little worried.
♬〜
Shun-san.
yeah?
I have to go soon
Kato-san...
Don't call his name.
♬〜
(Photon) It's taking a lot of time.
Anyway, let me break up soon.
Because of that woman
We'll also be happy to announce the marriage proposal we've prepared! ➡
📱 If you're slurping ➡
A reward for the hard work
You'll be missing it. ➡
Hugging quickly
Make it even with fait accompli!
♬〜
Sorry, sorry for keeping you waiting.
(Yugo) No. Was it okay?
Huh?
(Yugo) Ah
To the CEO, about me and Hattori-san ➡
Because it seems I misunderstood.
Ah, it's completely fine.
Because the misunderstanding was cleared.
Ah, that's right.
yes.
Rather
You can see Shun's new side ➡
It was good...
Ah... ah, listen over it.
sorry.
♬〜
Ah, pain Isn't it continuing?
(Yugo)
Huh? Ah, it's fine now.
good. Ah lunch
It was really tasty.
Thank you for the meal.
Huh?
Hattori will continue to do so ➡
Confidence to continue to interact with the CEO
Is there?
(Yugo) President's ➡
I've heard there are a lot of marriage proposals coming.
The president's private life ➡
Also around
It has a big impact. ➡
He is the president and heir.
There's too much to bear.
To Hattori-san ➡
Because of my partner
I don't want you to be hurt. ➡
So closer ➡
Someone who can protect Hattori-san
I think it's better to choose.
Like me.
What...
(Yugo) Didn't you notice? ➡
Since the first time we met ➡
forever
I was curious about you. ➡
About me
I wonder if they'll look at it that way.
Not the president ➡
I want you to choose me.
♬〜
she
He's an important person to me.
Such an ordinary woman
Isn't it easy to drop?
Even if you give me one
That's fine!
Sorry for getting involved in this.
Understood. I'm breaking up with Shun.